http://www.newser.com/privacy.aspx

Breaking News
Newser Privacy Policy
Please read this Privacy Policy (last revised as of January 31, 2018) before using this service. By continuing to use Newser.com, you acknowledge that you have read and agree to the terms of this policy.
Newser, LLC., the operator of www.Newser.com (the “Newser Website,” referred to as “Newser,” “us,” “we” or “our”) respects the privacy of our users, and we want you to be aware of how we use information that we have collected from and about you. By coming to the Newser Website, you are agreeing to and accepting this Privacy Policy as well as the User Agreement governing our services.
Because the Internet is a rapidly evolving medium, and enhancements to the services we provide may affect the information that we collect and the manner that we use it, the Privacy Policy may change from time to time. If it does, we will post the revised Privacy Policy on the Newser Website, with an indication of the date of the most recent revisions.
You should be aware that this Privacy Policy applies only to the Newser Website. Any websites linked to from the Newser Website, an advertisement or an article displayed on the site are governed by their own privacy policies.
What personally identifiable information do I provide to Newser, and how does Newser use it?
Personally identifiable information refers to any information that identifies or can be used to identify, contact or locate you. Newser collects only the personally identifiable information that you provide to us if you register as a registered user on the Newser Website, such as your name and e-mail address.
Newser uses your personally identifiable information to communicate with you regarding your account or the Newser Website. These communications may include, without limitation, notices regarding material changes to the Newser Website’s policies, service updates, and service enhancements. Since these account-related communications are necessary to ensure we provide our users with the highest quality of services, our users are not permitted to opt out from receipt of these communications.
Newser may also use personally identifiable information to e-mail you newsletters or tips about how to use the service, inform you of product updates, or notify you about our own special offers or those of our third-party partners. You may choose at any time to opt out of receiving some or all of these communications by emailing us here or by using the unsubscribe link on any e-mail message you receive.
In order to improve and create a more customized experience, Newser associates your personally identifiable information with information about your use of the website.
What other information is collected about me on the Newser Website and by whom?
Like most websites, Newser employs cookies to recognize you and your access privileges on the Newser Website. A cookie is a small piece of information that a website can store in a designated file on your computer. When you visit a site, that site can access only the information which it stored in your cookie – not information put on your computer by other web-based services.
Newser maintains internal logs of users’ use of the Newser Website. Logs include information such as IP address, browser type and version, and computer operating system. Newser uses logs mainly for systems administration and diagnostic purposes, and to detect improper use of the site. Logs may also be used to generate aggregate, non-personally identifiable information for advertisers or other third parties.
Newser may also contract, from time to time, with third parties to help us understand how people use our website and to provide functionalities such as email distribution, ad serving, customer surveys, comments, and content sharing. These companies also use cookies. They may also use other tracking technologies, such as web beacons (also known as clear GIFs, web bugs, tracking pixels or action tags), which are similar in function to cookies, allowing them to determine when users have reached particular web pages on the Newser Website.
Cookies and web beacons allow Newser and its third-party service providers to collect and analyze aggregate information about how its website is used.
We also allow third-party companies to collect certain information within our email newsletters. These companies may place an anonymous cookie and use a de-identified, non-human readable version of your email address for matching to other data collected from (or across) sites about you to improve the relevance of online advertising and personalization. Never is your actual email address shared with any company.
We sell advertising on our site so that we can provide our service for free. In the course of serving advertisements to this site, our third-party advertisers may place or recognize cookies and similar tracking technologies such as the Common ID cookie. Cookies are important devices for measuring advertising effectiveness and ensuring a robust online advertising industry.
Information about your visit, such as number of times you have viewed an ad (but not your name, address, or other personal information), is used to serve ads to you. The Common ID cookie stores a unique user ID in the first party domain and is accessible to our ad partners. This simple ID can be utilized to improve user matching, especially for delivering ads to iOS and MacOS browsers. Users can opt out of the Common ID tracking cookie by clicking here. Please be aware that if you opt out of allowing our web advertising partner to collect this information, you may not be able to use certain parts of the site nor have access to certain functions.
When you use our site, pre-selected companies may access and use certain information on your device and about your interests to serve ads or personalized content. If you’d like to opt out from receiving targeted advertisements from those companies that have placed an advertising cookie on your computer, mobile device, or other similar device, please click here or on the links below.
How is my personally identifiable information or site usage data used?
Newser may share your personally identifiable information with others under the types of circumstances described in this Privacy Policy. We also reserve the right to assign, sell, license, or otherwise transfer to a third party your personally identifiable information in connection with an assignment, sale, joint venture, or other transfer of all or substantially all of our assets.
We may make personally identifiable information available without your prior written or electronic consent, as required by law, court order, or as requested by other government or law enforcement authority.
Advertisements, promotional offers, promotional e-mails, newsletters, "free gifts," and links, for example, on the Newser Website or sent via e-mail or other means from Newser may ask for personally identifiable information from you. If you choose to provide this information, your personally identifiable information may be provided (either directly from you or by Newser) to the advertiser or website or company making the offer or providing the gift. This Privacy Policy does not cover the privacy and information practices of those advertisers or websites linked to the Newser Website.
Newser may use other companies and persons to perform certain functions for us. These functions might include, for example, providing customer service and sending e-mail.
These other companies and persons may have access to customer information (such as personally identifiable information) that is needed to perform their functions, but they are not authorized to use it for any other purposes. In addition, we may share information with other affiliated companies and joint ventures.
We may use and/or distribute information about you and your use of the Newser Website in ways that do not identify you individually or reveal your identity.
Demographic information provided by you may be used, among other things, to tailor your user experience at the Newser Website, distribute and show you content that we think you might be interested in, and display site content according to your preferences.
How secure is my personal information?
We are very concerned about the security of customer data. All personal information is password protected and all passwords are encrypted.
How do I opt out of targeted advertistments?
If you'd like to opt out from receiving targeted advertisements from those companies that have placed an advertising cookie on your computer, mobile device, or other similar device, please click on the links below.
Digital Advertising Alliance: http://www.aboutads.info/choices
Network Advertising Initiative:http://www.networkadvertising.org
JumpTap: https://opt.jumptap.com/optout/opt
How will I know when there are changes to this Privacy Policy?
This Privacy Policy is subject to modification from time to time at Newser’s discretion. All changes will be incorporated into the written policy and posted on the privacy policy pages of the Newser Website.
The date of last revision to the policy is indicated at the top of the document.
What if I have questions that are not answered here?
If you have questions, you may contact:
Newser, LLC.
1395 Brickell Avenue, Suite 800
Miami, Florida 33131
Attention:
General Counsel
Or, use this form.
Newser In Your Inbox
Get The Morning 8: The eight stories you need to know, bright and early.
© 2020 Newser, LLC. All rights reserved.
We see that you're using an ad-blocker.
To read our stories, you'll need to
turn off your ad-blocker.
As an advertising-supported site,
Newser can't exist without ads.
Turn off your ad-blocker
(for Newser only)
One last step.
You have to do this part yourself.
But you're a smartie, and we'll help you out.
1. Click on your ad-blocker icon in your browser.
(It might look like this
or this
or this
)
2. Every ad-blocker is a bit different, but look for
an option like disable, whitelist, or trust and click it.
Thanks so much.
We use cookies. By Clicking "OK" or any content on this site, you agree to allow cookies to be placed. Read more in our privacy policy.
OK
